https://www.symbolarts.com/privacy-policy/

PROTECTION OF INFORMATION
SymbolArts values the trust its customers place in the company. Accordingly, SymbolArts adheres to the highest ethical standards in gathering, using and safeguarding customer information that is entrusted to the company.
USE AND COLLECTION OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION
SymbolArts does not rent, sell or exchange information about its customers. Access to information about SymbolArts customers is restricted to the SymbolArts family of businesses. Third parties that need access to SymbolArts customer information in order to provide operational or other support services to SymbolArts must agree to safeguard customer information in strict compliance with SymbolArts policy. SymbolArts gathers only the customer information that is needed to administer its business, provide superior service and communicate offers on merchandise and services that SymbolArts believes will be of interest to its customers. SymbolArts limits access to customer information to those employees who need it to carry out their business functions. SymbolArts educates its employees about SymbolArts policies and practices in regard to safeguarding customer information; preventing its unauthorized access, use or disclosure; and, ensuring its proper handling.
ACCURACY AND SECURITY OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION
SymbolArts makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that the customer information it maintains is accurate, timely and secure. SymbolArts will monitor and adopt, as appropriate, new technological developments that are designed to aid in ensuring the accuracy and security of customer information. SymbolArts enforces its policies in regard to gathering, access and use of personal customer information by its employees and authorized third parties.
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
SymbolArts World Wide Web sites collect personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) from Web site visitors only when visitors voluntarily provide such information to SymbolArts. SymbolArts Web site visitors who do not want their personally identifiable information collected online are asked not to submit such information to SymbolArts. SymbolArts Web site visitors are informed that when they provide SymbolArts with personally identifiable information online, that information is kept within the SymbolArts family of businesses. Visitors are further informed that, unless specifically stated otherwise, the personally identifiable information may be stored and used by SymbolArts to better understand its customers’ needs, to improve SymbolArts products and services, and to contact customers regarding offers that may be of interest to them. If SymbolArts Web site visitors previously provided their e-mail addresses to SymbolArts and would like to have their e-mail addresses removed from SymbolArts e-mail mailing lists, SymbolArts asks them to send an e-mail message to webmaster@symbolarts.com. SymbolArts informs such visitors that it will use reasonable efforts to delete their e-mail addresses from its existing files.
CHILDREN
SymbolArts has no intention of collecting personally identifiable information (name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) from children (individuals under the age of 13) online and using that information for marketing purposes. If a child has provided SymbolArts with an e-mail address, SymbolArts asks that a parent or guardian of the child contact SymbolArts at webmaster@symbolarts.com if they would like the e-mail address deleted from SymbolArts e-mail mailing lists. SymbolArts informs customers that it will use reasonable efforts to delete such e-mail addresses from its existing files.
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY
SymbolArts Web Sites may collect information from Web site visitors that is not personally-identifiable, including the visitor’s operating system, browser, domain name, and the specific web pages on the SymbolArts Web site that are accessed or visited. SymbolArts only collects this information in the aggregate, and only uses it to improve SymbolArts Web sites.
INFORMATION PLACED AUTOMATICALLY ON VISITORS’ COMPUTERS
SymbolArts informs Web site visitors that when they visit SymbolArts Web sites, SymbolArts may store some information on the visitor’s computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. These files allow SymbolArts to tailor a Website to reflect a customer’s listed or historical preferences. Most Web browsers allow Web users to exercise control over such files on their computers by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying the user when such a file is stored. SymbolArts Web site visitors are asked to refer to their browser’s instructions to learn about those functions.
